People always called Nancy the little woman... They'll never do that again!
Attack of the 50 Ft. Woman is a science fiction, comedy, tv
movie film directed by Christopher Guest.
When an abused heiress grows to giant size because of her encounter with aliens, she
decides to get revenge on her cheating husband and those who looked down on her.
Nancy Archer, played by Daryl Hannah.
Harry Archer, played by Daniel Baldwin.
Hamilton Cobb, played by William Windom.
Dr. Theodora Cushing, played by Frances Fisher.
Louise 'Honey' Parker, played by Cristi Conaway.
Dr. Victor Loeb, played by Paul Benedict.
National Lampoon's Attack of the 5 Ft.
Women is an American 1994 Showtime television film that parodies two sensational news stories from the
1990s: the Tonya Harding-Nancy Kerrigan incident, and the John and Lorena Bobbitt incident.
The film is presented as a double feature, with
Julie Brown starring in both segments.
The title is a takeoff of Attack of the 50 Foot Woman.
The film explores themes of giant monster, alien, remake, camp humour.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.